[SPEAKER_01] I've seen the summers, the fall and winters
我见过夏日、秋日与冬日
[SPEAKER_01] Reaching for the moon
伸手触碰月亮
[SPEAKER_01] I've walked a thousand miles just to be here
我跋涉千里只为抵达此处
[SPEAKER_01] And not a day too soon
恰逢其时，不早不晚
[SPEAKER_01] Looking back at the life that we had, the things that we've been through.
回望我们共度的生活，经历过的种种
[SPEAKER_01] Remember this day, as I go my way, that leads me back to you.
请铭记今日，当我踏上归途，那条引我回到你身边的路
[SPEAKER_01] When the lights don't place, the music fades, and I've done all I can do.
当灯光不再亮起，音乐渐渐消逝，我已竭尽所能
[SPEAKER_01] Don't be afraid to walk alone Cause I'm on my way to you
别害怕独自前行，因为我正朝你走来
[SPEAKER_01] Soon a new face will take up my place, a circle will renew.
很快会有新面孔接替我的位置，循环将重新开始
[SPEAKER_01] Another chapter, forever after, I know I'll see you soon.
新的篇章，永恒之后，我知道很快会与你重逢
[SPEAKER_01] When I lost no place, the music fades, and I've done all I can do.
当我无处可去，音乐渐渐消逝，我已竭尽所能
[SPEAKER_01] Don't be afraid to walk alone Cause I'm on my way to you
别害怕独自前行，因为我正朝你走来